https://instrumentfind.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Instrument Find is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers and other users of the Instrument Find Website (all capitalized terms not defined in this Notice have the same meanings as in Instrument Find’s Website Terms of Use). Instrument Find created this Privacy Policy to give You confidence as You visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of Your privacy.This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Website, and not to any Third-Party Websites, which, as further explained below, may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.  Nor is this Privacy Policy applicable to information provided to Instrument Find in connection with transactions occurring other than by means of the Website.
BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY.  IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.
1.  CHANGES
EACH TIME YOU USE THE WEBSITE, THE THEN-CURRENT VERSION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL APPLY.  ALTHOUGH MOST CHANGES ARE LIKELY TO BE MINOR, Instrument Find RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME, NOTICE OF ANY SUCH CHANGE TO BE GIVEN BY THE POSTING OF A REVISED VERSION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND/OR A CHANGE NOTICE.  ACCORDINGLY, EACH TIME YOU USE THE WEBSITE, YOU SHOULD CHECK THE DATE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY (WHICH APPEARS AT THE END) AND, IF LATER THAN YOUR LAST VISIT TO THE WEBSITE, REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOR CHANGES.  IF YOU FIND ANY CHANGE UNACCEPTABLE, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE AND CEASE TO USE THE WEBSITE.  Unless Instrument Find obtains Your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected by Instrument Find after such revised Privacy Policy takes effect, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policies.
2. ELIGIBILITY TO USE WEBSITE
The Website is hosted and operated from within the United States.  As stated in the Terms of Use, use of the Website is restricted to United States residents 18 years of age or older. Instrument Find does not intend to, and will not knowingly, collect information from or about individuals located outside the United States or individuals younger than 18 years of age.
3. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES
(a) Traffic Data.  Like most website operators, Instrument Find gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including:  (i) IP addresses (ii) domain servers (iii) types of computers accessing the Website and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Website (collectively “Traffic Data”).  Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify You.
(b) Cookies.  A “Cookie” is a string of information that a website stores on a user&amprsquos computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website.  The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Website.  Gadgetreview may use Cookies to customize Your experience on the Website to Your presumed interests, to ensure that You do not see the same advertisements or informational messages repeatedly, and to store Your user name and password so You do not have to re-enter them each time You visit the Website.  For additional information on Gadgetreview’s use of Cookies, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies, below.
IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSER TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES.  IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.
This Privacy Policy applies only to Personal Information gathered by means of the Website. Instrument Find may supplement the Personal Information gathered by means of the Website with additional information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) that may lawfully provide such information to Instrument Find such supplemental information is not covered by this Privacy Policy.  Nor does this Privacy Policy apply to information provided by You to Third-Party Websites, which, as discussed above and below, may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.
YOU ARE UNDER NO OBLIGATION TO PROVIDE PERSONAL INFORMATION, WITH THE CAVEAT THAT YOUR REFUSAL TO DO SO MAY PREVENT YOU FROM USING CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE OR FROM MAKING PURCHASES OR RESERVATIONS BY MEANS OF THE WEBSITE.
4.  INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES
(a)  Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies. Instrument Find may analyze Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help Instrument Find and Instrument Find’s licensors and suppliers better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it.  By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Instrument Find is able to better design the Website to improve Your experience, and to serve You more relevant and interesting content and advertisements.  From time to time, Instrument Find may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website.  Other than by using cookies to store Your user name and password, Instrument Find does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personal Information.
(b) Personal Information
(i)  Generally. Instrument Find uses Your Contact Data to send You information about Instrument Find and Instrument Find’s goods and services, to contact You as necessary in connection with Your transactions with Instrument Find, and to send You other communications that You have agreed to receive. Instrument Find uses Your Financial Data to verify Your qualifications for certain goods and/or services, and to charge You for Your for transactions with Instrument Find. Instrument Find uses Your Demographic Data to customize and tailor Your experience on the Website. Instrument Find uses Your Transactional Data to fulfill its obligations in connection with Your transactions, and to provide customer service to You.  As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies, from time to time Instrument Find may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website.
(ii)  Disclosure in Connection with Provision of Goods and Services. Instrument Find may disclose Personal Information to those who help it provide the goods and services made available by means of the Website, including the suppliers of those goods and services and those who perform technical, administrative and data processing tasks such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security.  The third parties to whom Instrument Find discloses Personal Information all have agreed to abide by this Privacy Policy with respect to the information provided to them by Instrument Find (although, as discussed below, some of those third parties have separate privacy policies that govern their collection, use and storage of information that You provide to them directly).
(iii)  Other Disclosure. Instrument Find also discloses Personal Information under the following circumstances:
By Law or to Protect Rights – Instrument Find discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Instrument Find believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Instrument Find, third parties or the public at large.
Marketing Communications – As stated in the Terms of Use, by using the Website, You consent to receive from Instrument Find periodic email communications regarding Instrument Find products and services. Instrument Find may also provide Your Contact Information to third parties, so that they may contact You directly with information about additional products and services that Instrument Find believes may be of interest to You (”Marketing Communications”).  You may opt-out of having Your Contact Information provided to third parties for the purpose of Marketing Communications, by contacting Instrument Find at info@instrumentfind.com.  For additional information, see the section concerning User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information, below.  Even after opting-out, You may continue to receive Marketing Communications from third parties to whom Instrument Find already has provided Your Contact Information.  You will be responsible for contacting those third parties directly to request that You receive no further Marketing Communications.  You are under no obligation to receive Marketing Communications, with the caveat that Your refusal to do so may prevent You from making purchases or reservations by means of the Website. Instrument Find will not itself, and will not provide mobile telephone Contact Information to others to, send Marketing Communications via mobile telephone text message.
Business Transfers Bankruptcy – Instrument Find reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Instrument Find’s assets.  Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if You are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it.  Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by Gadgetreview&amprsquos successor organization.
Unpaid Accounts – If You fail to pay any balance owed in consideration of any transaction with Instrument Find, Instrument Find may, as permitted by law, report Your Personal Information, including without limitation Your Financial Data and Transactional Data, to consumer credit reporting services, collection agencies and others.
5. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Instrument Find has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of Your Personal Information.
6. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION
Instrument Find wants Your Personal Information to be complete and accurate.  As stated in the Website Terms of Use, by using the Website, You represent and warrant that all information You provide in connection with any Reservation, Application or otherwise in connection with Your use of the Website will be complete and accurate, and that You will update that information as necessary to maintain its completeness and accuracy.  To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to, Your Personal Information, visit Your personal profile at Gadgetreview.com.  Through Your personal profile You may review and update Your Personal Information that we have already collected.
7.  THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES
Instrument Find neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites.  Accordingly, the operators of Third-Party Websites, including without limitation Vendors, are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personal Information provided directly to them by Instrument Find.  Before visiting or providing information to a Third-Party Website, You should inform Yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website, and should take those steps necessary to, in Your discretion, protect Your privacy.
The Site contains links to web sites of third parties. (Publisher) is not responsible for the actions of these third parties, including their privacy practices and any content posted on their web sites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use personal information. (Publisher) adheres to industry recognized standards to secure any personal information in our possession, and to secure it from unauthorized access and tampering. However, as is true with all online actions, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions of personal information, or other users of the Site may misuse or abuse your personal information that they may collect from the Site.
(Publisher) uses third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Site. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1×1 pixel .gifs or web beacons to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our website and other websites, but will not collect any information which can personally identify you or can be linked to you. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, and the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, currently you may either visit each ad network’s web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. Click here for the NAI gateway opt-out site.
This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies’ privacy policies.
8.  PROMOTIONAL ACTIVITIES
From time to time, Instrument Find may conduct contests, giveaways and other promotions (collectively, “Promotional Activities”).  Any information submitted in connection with Promotional Activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  From time to time, Instrument Find may also ask You to participate in surveys designed to help Instrument Find improve the Website.  Any Personal Information provided to Instrument Find in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in aggregated form.
Subscribe to our list
Don't worry, we don't spam
For customers
Product for review
Contact Us
Best deals
Catalog
For vendors
Testimonial
How to use
Donate Us
Catalog
Sign Up for Weekly Newsletter Investigationes demonstraverunt lectores legere me lius quod ii legunt saepius.
Disclosure Instrument Find strives to keep its information accurate and up to date. The information in our reviews could be different from what you find when visiting a financial institution, service provider or a specific product’s website. All products are presented without warranty.
Follow Us
How We Review Our reviews come from trusted musicians with experience in performing on these instruments and having recordings of these instruments to judge their durability, look and sound. Each music instrument review has a description, rating, pros/cons and pricing so you can easily compare.
Navigation
About Us
Contact Us
How We Review
Information
Accessibility
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
© 2020 Instrument Find. All rights reserved.
Subscribe to our list
Don't worry, we don't spam
Login/Register access is temporary disabled
